[
    {"question":" ____ what did Jimmi Hendrix play his guitar, left handed or right handed?","answer":"Witch"},
    {"question":" How many Oscars Joan ____ Crawford win?","answer":"did"},
    {"question":" Which feature ____ common to Emmenthal and Gruyere cheeses?","answer":"is"},
    {"question":" What metric measurement was originally defined as a ten millionth of the distance ____ the equator to the pole?","answer":"from"},
    {"question":" ____ area of Paris was the setting of the film  'Can - Can' ?","answer":"What"},
    {"question":" What is the most common language ____ in Algeria?","answer":"spoken"},
    {"question":" Which European capital city did Ernest Hemmingway refer to____ 'the capital of the world' ?","answer":"as"},
    {"question":" Which two of the four evangelists were ____ apostles?","answer":"also"},
    {"question":" Which Asian leader was in prison when time magazine named ____ man of the year for 1930?","answer":"him"},
    {"question":" What is a Gametophobic bachelor afraid ____ ?","answer":"of"},
    {"question":" Chives are the cousin of ____ vegetable?","answer":"which"},
    {"question":" What is the ____ in this sequence: Alpha, beta, gamma, delta...?","answer":"next"},
    {"question":" What is the ____ name of Mary Shelley's tragic hero Baron Frankenstein ?","answer":"first"},
    {"question":" Which famous ____ sculptor created  The Thinker and  The Kiss?","answer":"French"},
    {"question":" Emperor Shahjahan's monument to his favorite wife ____ completed in Agra in 1563. What is it ?","answer":"was"},
    {"question":" Which Barcelona ____ designed many distinctive buildings including the church of the Sagrada Familia ?","answer":"architect"},
    {"question":" The herb 'wild marjoram' is ____ known by what name ?","answer":"better"},
    {"question":" What was Pedro Duque the first ____ to do ?","answer":"Spaniard"},
    {"question":" The Boston Tea Party contributed to the ____ of which war ?","answer":"star"},
    {"question":" ____ what film has Al Pacino won his only Oscar ?","answer":"For"}
 ]